Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Cartoons/Collages, 1964, 1970-2008, undated; 20 Linear Feet in .5 record carton, 44 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 3 oversize flat folders, 1 flat-file folder
  - Rockin Karl, undated (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Rolls -- Royce (2), 1982 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Russian Rich, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Sane Edward's, undated (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Save Everything, undated (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Scab Beer, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Schmidt, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - Sell the Right Thing, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Slice of Pie, undated (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Smart Feller, undated (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - South Africa Trains, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Capitalists Forge Ahead, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - Stop the World, undated (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - Suck Authority, 1983 (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - Superior Like Us, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - T.M. and the Maoris, undated (Box 135, Folder 28)
  - They Steal H, undated (Box 135, Folder 29)
  - Timex, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 30)
  - Trotsky, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 31)
  - U.S. Out of North America, undated (Box 135, Folder 32)
  - Uprising of the Pedlariat, undated (Box 135, Folder 33)
  - Wall St. / Hungry and Homeless, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 34)
  - War...Wanna Fuck?, undated (Box 135, Folder 35)
  - We Owe 4 Trillion Dollars!, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 36)
  - Welfare Chiselers, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 37)
  - Welfare Scum, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 38)
  - Where's the Herb Goin?, undated (Box 135, Folder 39)
  - Who Do Ya Love, undated (Box 135, Folder 40)
  - Why Note Book 'Em?, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 41)
  - Yank Go Home, 2000 (Box 135, Folder 42)
  - Yeltsin Tantsin, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 43)
  - My Twins and A Bomb Rads, 2000 (Box 135, Folder 44)
  - Shitle of Liberty Bomb, circa 1985-1994 (Box 135, Folder 45)
  - Jews -- Where is My Wandering Jew, circa 1985-1994 (Box 135, Folder 46)
  - Uranus, 2002 (Box 135, Folder 47)
  - Goodbye Dolly, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 48)
  - Einstein Never Wore Socks, undated (Box 135, Folder 49)
  - Possible Futures and Possible Illustration, 2004-2006 (Box 135, Folder 50)
  - Mea Culpalicity, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 51)
  - The Golf Links, circa 1990-2010 (Box 135, Folder 52)
  - Broadway -- 1888 Original, undated (Box 135, Folder 53)
  - Porn King, 2001 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Onion, 2008 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Sheik Condom, 2001 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Poin, 2003 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Waterboarding, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Tastee Harvard, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - That's Post-Modernism for Ya, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Bob Dylan and Christianity, 1979-1986 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - To Do -- Great Moments...Photo, undated (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Great Moments in the History of Sex, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Great Moments in American History -- Amazing Bribes, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Don't Give A, 2001 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Take That!, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Feast of Fools, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Norton's Folly, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Hughes, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - Abbie Called, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Absolut, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Agent, undated (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - Airline Controllers, circa 1981-1989 (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - Argentine Jew Art, undated (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - Armando Shmuck Series, undated (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - Tuli Cartoons at Patterson Show, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 23)
  - Art Forgeries, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 24)
  - Bank Robber, undated (Box 136, Folder 25)
  - Buddha Divests, 1989-2007 (Box 136, Folder 26)
  - Bush: Forget Our Troubles, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 27)
  - Can't Dance -- Keep Your Revolution, 1988, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 28)
  - Cartoon Ideas, circa 1996 (Box 136, Folder 29)
  - Cheery Vinyl Decay, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 30)
  - The CIA was Eating Beans, 1985 (Box 136, Folder 31)
  - Clinton Campaign Songs, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 32)
  - Columbus, undated (Box 136, Folder 33)
  - Contructivist Cartoon, undated (Box 136, Folder 34)
  - Cutest Cock, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 35)
  - Dallas, circa 1983 (Box 136, Folder 36)
  - Dario Fo, 1983, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 37)
  - Don't Care What Kind of Communist, undated (Box 136, Folder 38)
  - Dow -- Corning -- Bush and Rules, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 39)
  - Draft Card and CIA, undated (Box 136, Folder 40)
  - Drug Kingpins No. 1, 2001 (Box 136, Folder 41)
  - Duck You, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 42)
  - Duplicates, 1983-1996 (Box 136, Folder 43-44)
  - Duplicates and Variants -- Do No Use, 1983-1993, undated (Box 136, Folder 45)
  - Einstein, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Emerging Collective, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Employed Artist, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Ethnic Humor, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Evolution, [Lennon], 1988 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Expanding (Bush) Economy, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Family Link to Criminality (Bush and Son), 1992 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Family Values, undated (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Filmore, undated (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - First Amendment, undated (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Food Chain, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - For Bob Newman -- Miscellaneous Cartoons, 1990-1994 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Forbes Horsemen, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Fotostats, 1983-1985 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Framed, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Fuck the Flag, undated (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Fuck the Pigs, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Funny Times (Mixed), undated (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Get Even, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Get Off My Land, undated (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - Good For You Too and Gangbang, 1991, undated (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - Govt Sux, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism, 1992, undated (Box 137, Folder 23)
  - Great Moments -- Mixed, 1995, undated (Box 137, Folder 24)
  - Great Moments in Philosophy, 1997 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  - Guccione, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 26)
  - Hold, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 27)
  - I am a Poet, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 28)
  - If Only the Czar Knew, circa 1981-1989 (Box 137, Folder 29)
  - Important Artist, undate (Box 137, Folder 30)
  - Jack Cantors Funeral, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 31)
  - Jackson Hates Coke, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 32)
  - Jeff Messerschmidt -- Commissions, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 33)
  - Kennebunkport, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 34)
  - Layoffs No Threat, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 35)
  - Lenin vs. Lennon, undated (Box 137, Folder 36)
  - Let Teachers Fight, undated (Box 137, Folder 37)
  - Libertarian, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 38)
  - Lost Leaders / It's All Lies, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 39)
  - The Love of Possessions, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 40)
  - Meat -- Mixed, undated (Box 137, Folder 41)
  - Memory and Desire, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 42)
  - Miss Universe, undated (Box 137, Folder 43)
  - Money Cover, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 44)
  - Money Talks, undated (Box 137, Folder 45)
  - The More Things Derange..., 1991 (Box 137, Folder 46)
  - Mulroney, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 47)
  - Multi-Party System, undated (Box 137, Folder 48)
  - Neo-Shill Media, 2004-2005 (Box 137, Folder 49)
  - New Body Bag, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 50)
  - New Frankness in Jeans, undated (Box 137, Folder 51)
  - New Year, circa 1980-1989 (Box 137, Folder 52)
  - New York Press Cartoons, undated (Box 137, Folder 53)
  - New York Great, undated (Box 137, Folder 54)
  - NLCRA, undated (Box 137, Folder 55)
  - No Personality, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 56)
  - Original Cartoons, 1985-1990 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Originals -- Genital Cartoons, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Panama -- Kinder, Gentler, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - PAND -- Without a Song, undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Pardon Bush, 1992 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Pawn -- Porn, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Peacemaker, undated (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Perot, 1992 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Poor -- You Always Have Within You, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Prick, undated (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Printed Matter, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Privatize -- ACLU, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Public Art, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Reagan Wouldn't Know Good Taste, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Run for Your Money, undated (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Russian Banks, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Sadat, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Second Choices, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Shit -- Pen, undated (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Single Note, undated (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Stock Exchange, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Tenement, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Thelma Blitz Colorizations, undated (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - Those Who Can't; Art, undated (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Three Jokers / New Order, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - Too Many Indians, undated (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - Toos Pore L'Art, undated (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - Trickle Down Theory, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - Trotsky, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - Truth Party, undated (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - USA -- USSR, circa 1980-1991 (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - Voter, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 32)
  - War Carts, 1986, undated (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - War -- Mixed, 1982-1985 (Box 138, Folder 34)
  - Wars and US History, 1984, undated (Box 138, Folder 35)
  - What's at the Top?, undated (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - Whitewash, circa 1983 (Box 138, Folder 37)
  - Who Will Pay the Economists?, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 38)
  - Who'll Take Care of Poopsie?, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 39)
  - Why am I Not Asleep?, undated (Box 138, Folder 40)
  - Why Primates Laughing?, 1992 (Box 138, Folder 41)
  - Will Be Lazy for Food, undated (Box 138, Folder 42)
  - Yeltsin for Bush, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 43)
  - Youth Wasted on Young, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 44)
  - Dentist -- Circumcision -- What Have I Got -- High School Suicides, 1997-1998 (Box 138, Folder 45)
  - Aids Cure -- Intensive Care -- Dying of Cancer -- American Medical, 1987-1996, undated (Box 138, Folder 46)
  - New Doctor -- What Good are Kids -- Hooray for Hollywood -- Megalomycin -- Okla-Michigan Bomb, 1984-1995 (Box 138, Folder 47)
  - Private Prisons -- Great Moments in the History of Journalism and America, 1972-1995 (Box 138, Folder 48)
  - Fighter Pilot -- Stray Bullets -- Poor Babies -- How to Tie a Scarf, 1988-1990 (Box 138, Folder 49)
  - Miss Education -- Finding an Apartment -- Scalping Knives, 1974-2003 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Great Moments in the History of the New York City / Cartoon Research Material, 1977-1978 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Alberto Gonzales, undated (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Twyn Source Stuff, undated (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Twyn, undated (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Judges, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Worm, undated (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - One Foot Hung Jury, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Whipped Police, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - God Talks to Cops, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Bullets that Change America, undated (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Hialeah, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Scalp Em, undated (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - US Leads Child Gun Fatalities, 1995-1997 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Clint-Hyp Kasovo -- Littleton, 1993-1999 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Guns Don't Kill People, undated (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Yoko, 1980-1981 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - 10,000 Guns -- USA, undated (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Get Wisdom, undated (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - The Bull Toils, undated (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Nuns, undated (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Grace Jones C-C #4, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - Banana Republic, undated (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Iraqi Schools, 2003 (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - War Vendors, 2003 (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Mail for FBI, 1987-2010 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Clint, 1984-1985 (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - Cop Shit, undated (Box 139, Folder 28)
  - Lawyers, undated (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - Asst. Detective (1908) via Bintel Brief, undated (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Baby Let Me Drive Your Ambulance, 2000 (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Law, 1972-1999 (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Gay CIA, 1983-1993 (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - The Plunger Lunger, undated (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - Clinton -- Original / Congratulations, undated (Box 139, Folder 35)
  - Piercing, undated (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - Winter Far Behind, undated (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Young Enuf, undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Head Start, undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Learn in School Today, undated (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Lower-Caste Indian Jobs, undated (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - John Reed and Harvard Review, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - B and W Impeach, 2004 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Estrogen, undated (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Will Rogers, 2007-2008 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - How Many are There?, undated (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - US Customs, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Kick in the Balls Oxford University, undated (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Kid Like a Yuppie, undated (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Poor Babies!, 1987-1993 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Cop Shop, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - I've Talked Enough Bout Myself, undated (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - 106 A Corpse, undated (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Van Gogh, undated (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Seven Arts, undated (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Absolut Death and Absolute Shit Advertising, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Whitman Said, undated (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - Bone Chance Gallery, undated (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - Rembrandt, undated (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - Door Stop, undated (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - Moon Over Soho, undated (Box 140, Folder 25)
  - It's Nothing, undated (Box 140, Folder 26)
  - Gauguin -- School of Visual Arts, undated (Box 140, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Kipnis, undated (Box 140, Folder 28)
  - Artists and Government, 1981-1996 (Box 140, Folder 29)
  - The Children Art Union, undated (Box 140, Folder 30)
  - Art Strike, undated (Box 140, Folder 31)
  - Art is a Weapon, undated (Box 140, Folder 32)
  - Do I Contradict Myself, undated (Box 140, Folder 33)
  - Al Goldstein -- Screw, 1996, undated (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Playboy, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Kool Kancer Concerts, 1983 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Better Grade of Cancer, undated (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Marx on Profit, undated (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Meataholics Delight, 2000 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Possible Cartoons and Collages, 1998-2001, undated (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Texass, undated (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Thatcher, 1992-2007 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Kill for Peace Again Originals, 1940-1986 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Safe Conduct Pass (Original), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - In Media Feces Originals, 1982-1985 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Original Drawings by Arab Kupa [Tuli Kupferberg] and Henry Gazess, 1942 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Cartoons and Original Drawings, undated (Box 141, Folder 14-16)
  - Original Drawings -- Unsigned, undated (Box 141, Folder 17-18, Box 142, Folder 1-2)
  - Beatles, Cretans, Van Gogh, 1987-1999 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Fashion, Woody, Cosby, 1965-2005 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Nobody for Prez, Space, Radio, 1986-2007 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Mao, Thatcher, Twain, 1990-2007 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Iraq, Remember Vietnam, 1994-2007 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Cartoons and Collages, 1983-2005 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Sports, Cable, Draft, 1984-1992 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Cartoons, 1985-1998 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Cartoon and Collage Research Material -- Clippings, 1983-2006 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Absolute Haring, 1990 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Children's Art Collective -- Art is a Weapon -- Art Strike, 1980-1990 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Do I Contradict Myself? -- What Makes a Good Cartoon?, 1987-1988 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Kipnis, Last of the Rootless Cosmopolitans, Van Gogh, Art / Government, 1984-1998 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - What Art Is, undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Gauguin, Blood Sculpture, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Grosz / Heartfield, undated (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Great Philosophical Questions -- Rembrandt -- Art Marketing Seminar, 1993-1996 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - George Segal, 1986-1993 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Whitman -- Seven Arts -- Van Gogh, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Riot Police -- Kid Like a Yuppie -- The Great Cultural War, 1985-1992 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Kick in the Balls, Oxford -- Lawyer -- Worms -- U.S. Customs, 1992-1996 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Sting Operation -- How Many are There, 1990-1992 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Darling Daughter -- Will Rogers -- Estrogen -- Impeach the President Buttons, 2008, undated (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - NYPD -- John Reed / Harvard Review -- Harvard Emblem, 1984-2002 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Learned in School -- Preschool -- Young Enuff to Know Better, 1985-1999 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Piercing -- Jocelyn Elders -- Hitting, 1984-1995 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Plunger Lunger -- Cop Shit -- Gay CIA -- Baby Let Me Drive Your Ambulance, 1984-2000 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Ass't Detective -- Clinton -- Mail for the FBI, 1985-1998 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Grace Jones -- Iraq War -- Banana Republic, 1985-2003 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Nuns -- The Bull Tolls -- Kosovo / Littleton, 1990-1999 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Child Gun Fatalities -- Scalp 'Em -- Haleah -- Bullets That Changed America, 1997-1999 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - God Talks to A Cop -- Whipped Police -- Hung Jury -- Bribery Judge -- Worm Turned -- Judge's Salary, 1984-1989 (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Twyn -- Charles II, 1994-2000 (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Stalin the Executioner -- Alberto Gonzales -- Marxism, 1996-2007 (Box 143, Folder 24)
  - Marxism in Universities -- Perfectly Maladjusted -- Psychotic Marketing, 1992-1996 (Box 143, Folder 25)
  - Paranoids -- Freudian Slip -- Too Generous -- All Alone, 1990-1991 (Box 143, Folder 26)
  - Afraid of Broadway, undated (Box 143, Folder 27)
  - All the Doctors, undated (Box 143, Folder 28)
  - Art: 2DS, undated (Box 143, Folder 29)
  - Art Colony, 1990, undated (Box 143, Folder 30)
  - Be Happy in Your Work, undated (Box 143, Folder 31)
  - Beggars, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 32)
  - Bob [Dylan], undated (Box 143, Folder 33)
  - Book of Perverbs, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 34)
  - Bribe, circa 2001 (Box 143, Folder 35)
  - Cambell's Kids, circa 1996-2010 (Box 143, Folder 36)
  - Casablanca, undated (Box 143, Folder 37)
  - Cats, undated (Box 143, Folder 38)
  - Chesterfields Mass Murder, 1998 (Box 143, Folder 39)
  - CIA Killers -- Why?, 1997 (Box 143, Folder 40)
  - Cig -- Dealing Drugs, 1998 (Box 143, Folder 41)
  - Cigar Aficianado, 1996 (Box 143, Folder 42)
  - Coney Mob, undated (Box 143, Folder 43)
  - Crinoline, undated (Box 143, Folder 44)
  - The Dishonorables, circa 2000-2010 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Dog Better than Man, circa 1997-2010 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Don't Make Trouble, undated (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Dreamland / Foolish House, 2000 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Economist on Anarchy, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Einstein and Gravity, 2003 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Elvis, undated (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Elvis and Nixon, undated (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Employed Artist / Writer / Actor, undated (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Engineers for Glee, undated (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Exit Art, circa 2004-2010 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Feminists Against Censorship, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Flying Saucers, 2000 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Food Series, 1987 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - Forget?, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - French Images, undated (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Friendly Strangers, undated (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - From USPS Books, undated (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - The Fucking Dead, undated (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - Get that Communist, 2006 (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Harvard International Review, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Holly and Mistletoe, undated (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Home Planet Cover, circa 1991 (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - I Pretend to Work, undated (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - If the Rich Could Pay the Poor, 1995 (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - Illustrations to Use, undated (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Jingle Ass, 1997, undated (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - Joe Camel Fucks Bailey's, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 28)
  - Johnny Cash, undated (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - King Kong, undated (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - Kittens, undated (Box 144, Folder 31)
  - Labor Daze, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 32)
  - Love in Greenwich Village, circa 1995-2010 (Box 144, Folder 33)
  - Love Major, undated (Box 144, Folder 34)
  - Luna Park, undated (Box 144, Folder 35)
  - Marlene, undated (Box 144, Folder 36)
  - Men Kill for What I Give, undated (Box 144, Folder 37)
  - Millionaires, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 38)
  - Mixed Cartoons, undated (Box 144, Folder 39)
  - Mixed Images, undated (Box 144, Folder 40)
  - New Work, undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Noam and Chavez, 2003-2005 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Office Sinner, undated (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Only 21,000 Dead Canadians!, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Over-Much Niceness, undated (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Peacemaker (Mini), undated (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Piggy Pears, undated (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Possible, 2002, undated (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Possibles -- Older, undated (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Puck, 1999-2000 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Revolution -- Festival, 2001, undated (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - RNC 2004, 2004, undated (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Salute to American Ingenuity, 2003, undated (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Shit Mines, undated (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Snarl, undated (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Splintered Commie, undated (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - The State of the State, 2001 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - A Stupid Bastard, undated (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - To Do, undated (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Wall's Ice Cream, undated (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - Warfare Time, 2003 (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - We Arm the World, 2001 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - Welfare -- New Bill, 1996 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Wine Tits, circa 1995-2010 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - Worst Book, undated (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - Xmas, undated (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - Xmas Cards, undated (Box 145, Folder 27)
  - Cartoons, Collages -- Various, 2005, undated (Box 145, Folder 28)
  - If Living was a Thing Money Could Buy, 1987-1988, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 29)
  - Mailing Packet of Cartoons for "FOR" and "JPF", circa 2006 (Box 145, Folder 30)
  - Jane Greer Gallery Show: Questionable Cartoons, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 31)
  - Cartoons and Collages -- Bribe, 1991-1992 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Cartoons -- Poster Sized, 1992-2001, undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Hymie the Hippie -- Original Art, circa 1988-2010 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism, 1994, 2003, undated (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Karl Marx and Ethics of Capitalism, 1991-1993 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Great Moments in the History of Journalism, 1983-1994 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Cartoons/Collages, undated (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - New Cartoons -- Book of Perverbs, undated (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Recent Cartoons -- Great Moments in the History..., undated (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Ready to Mount -- Great Moments in the History of..., undated (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Labor 1 -- Do This Next -- Board This and Aphorisms, undated (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Labor 2, undated (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Teach Yourself Fucking -- Leftovers and Dups and Not Used, circa 1999-2000 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - War Cartoons, 2002, undated (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Thelma Goes Berserk, undated (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Healing for Money, 2000 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Help the Paranoids, undated (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - More Marxists in Factories, undated (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Aids Cure, undated (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Karl's Pub Crawl, undated (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Stalin and Lenin's Commissars, undated (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Dr.: What Have I Got?, undated (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Woman Doctor, undated (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Circumcision, undated (Box 148, Folder 20)
  - Dentist -- Sorry We're In, undated (Box 148, Folder 21)
  - Alone, undated (Box 148, Folder 22)
  - You're Too Generous, undated (Box 148, Folder 23)
  - Freudian Slip, undated (Box 148, Folder 24)
  - Private Prisons, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 25)